♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪
=Rise Again=
=Episode 17=
Moving the sword
is already no easy feat.
Didn't expect...
Grandpa.
Hurry, bring him to me.
(With skills like that,)
(I can feel at ease)
(letting Tian stay with him.)
Was that
immortal light?
Su Wubing definitely has the makings
of an immortal.
(Though it's not fully refined yet,)
(the immortal energy within)
(could help me recover my cultivation.)
How did you make it?
(The moment the divine sword appeared,)
(I felt an aura similar
to my family heirloom)
(spirit stone.)
One thing.
Come back with me.
No way.
Grandpa is waiting.
I've already pulled the sword.
Your bet...
Impossible.
That doesn't count. You cheated.
Cheated? In front of everyone?
Is the Gu family trying to back out now?
Weren't you pretty arrogant just now?
Mr. Gu.
A bet is a bet.
Su Wubing.
Just you wait.
Let's go.
Wubing.
This is my grandpa Fang Xianglin.
Grandpa, this is Su Wubing.
Have a seat.
You're very skilled.
Why have you stayed completely unknown
for the past twenty years?
Grandpa, he just doesn't like
showing off.
He's not hiding it on purpose.
I'm asking him, not you.
Some things are private.
I'd rather not say much.
But don't worry,
I'll always take care of Fang Tian.
With just that one sentence,
can I trust you with Tian?
That's a bit much to call trust.
Mr. Fang,
I was thinking
if you're really not at ease,
you should've taken Tian back.
Quick thinker, aren't you?
Tian, good eye.
This young man has a bright future.
Grandpa...
Since she is a member of your family,
why did you wait so long
to find her?
Wubing...
This is my fault.
Back then, with Fang family in chaos,
I had to send her away
to protect our bloodline.
All these years,
I've carried guilt in my heart.
I understand.
But whether she returns home,
it's up to her.
If she wants to go back,
I won't stop her.
If she wants to stay,
I'll keep taking care of her.
Alright.
With that, I'm relieved.
How about this.
When I go back,
I'll announce your marriage.
The wedding will be at the Fang family.
Grandpa, we're just like siblings.
Mr. Fang, you're joking, right?
What, you don't want it?
I have someone in my heart.
I can't marry Tian.
Could it be that girl Lin Ningxue?
Mr. Fang,
I've always treated Tian
like a little sister.
Either way,
I will continue to care for her.
Fine.
I won't meddle in
young people's affairs.
The Fang family doors
will always be open for you.
Tian,
today I'll hand this bronze mirror
to you.
This mirror contains
ancient divine power.
That's right.
This is
the Fang family's ancestral treasure.
Break it in a crisis,
and it can rewind time by one minute.
Whoever holds this mirror
is the head of the Fang family.
Today I formally pass it to Tian.
Come in.
You stole the spotlight
at the tournament.
Now the whole city knows
that my fiancé
is the one who pulled the divine sword.
I think it's a good thing.
At least from now on,
no one will dare mess
with the Lin family.
That's not what I want to say.
Wedding crash, saving my dad
and drawing the sword?
You've got way too many secrets.
Su Wubing,
we've been through so much.
Can't you tell me the truth yet?
You may find hard to accept
every word I'm about to say,
but it's all absolutely true.
You and I
were once immortal lovers.
But you're cursed by fate.
I once fought against the Heavenly Dao,
but in the end I couldn't save you.
So, I followed you
through reincarnation,
hiding from the Heavenly Dao.
You're saying
I still carry the Heavenly Dao's curse?
Then you...?
Ningxue.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Just a sudden headache.
Take me for a walk.
So it's because you regained
your memories
that you found me.
Yes.
I didn't tell you before.
Afraid you wouldn't believe me
And I was afraid
the Heavenly Dao would notice.
So Mr. Ye calling you "My Lord"
was also from your past life?
Him?
He's my subordinate,
and waited ten thousand years.
So none of it was coincidence.
It's destiny.
Ningxue,
I don't want
to lose you again in this life.
What would happen
if you broke the curse?
Any attempt to break it
is seen by Heavenly Dao as a challenge.
The Heavenly Dao
will strike immediately
and destroy both of our spiritual forms.
I used to think
the Lin family matters
and my dad's illness
were all my burden alone.
Sometimes it pressed down on me.
I could barely breathe.
But after I met you,
I finally understood
what it feels like
to have someone to lean on.
Ever since my father
passed the responsibility to me,
I haven't had the right
to live like an ordinary person...
to date, to live.
I don't even know how to run a company.
But I know clearly
someone has to step up
at times like this.
Luckily,
I met you.
I'm not afraid of fate or duty or curse,
because I can now
stay with you like this.
Ningxue!
Ningxue...
My Lord.
Holy Maiden.
Mr. Ye, just call me by my name.
Why choose this place?
The spiritual power is abundant here,
and Tianmiao has also set up a barrier.
If anything goes wrong,
Tianmiao can protect us.
Although you've retrieved
the Heavenly God Sword,
it still hasn't been refined.
I'm only one step away
from the Heavenly God Realm.
So what we can do now
is extend Ningxue's life.
Understood.
Then let's not waste any time.
♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪